{
    "1": {"question": "What is the difference between a tool and an implement?", "answer": "Tools have motors, implements do not such as combs, brushes, clips, shears"},
    "2": {"question": "What would be considered equipment?", "answer": "Other items in the shop, chairs, shampoo bowls, capes"},
    "3": {"question": "What type of comb is used for parting the hair?", "answer": "Rattail combs"},
    "4": {"question": "What type of comb is good for blending?", "answer": "Taper comb, different size teeth on both ends"},
    "5": {"question": "What brushes are used to blow-dry the hair?", "answer": "Vent-holes/slits in the back and round brushes - revved like motorcycle handle"},
    "6": {"question": "What is the preferred size of the shears?", "answer": "6.5 to 7.5"},
    "7": {"question": "What are brushes made of?", "answer": "Bristles, made of boar, plastic, or metal"},
    "8": {"question": "Name the parts of the clippers.", "answer": "Adjustment lever, moving/cutting blade, still blade, heel, on and off switch, and your set screw"},
    "9": {"question": "Name the parts of the shears.", "answer": "Thumb grip on moving blade, and still blade, pivot screw"},
    "10": {"question": "How often should you change your wet sanitizer solution?", "answer": "Daily"},
    "11": {"question": "Which curling iron requires a miniature stove?", "answer": "Conventional/Marcel"},
    "12": {"question": "Which electrical measurement measures the amount of power used in a second?", "answer": "Watt"},
    "13": {"question": "What is the first rule of mixing any chemical?", "answer": "Read the manufacturer's directions"},
    "14": {"question": "What are the 2 types of capes?", "answer": "Dry and wet"}
}


